<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>The Cyber Necronomicon</title>
    
    
    <description>Who the hell reads RSS feeds?</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>The Mental Struggle of WFH</title>
        <description>
          The Mental Struggle of WFH and overcomming lazyness and the Sarlacc pit of despair - 
          The Mental Struggle of WFH and Overcomming the Pit of Dispair Where you smashing out work for 12hours a day straight, felt like you were on a tredmill at equal pace to Usain Bolt during the 100m in 2014 and then all of a sudden you got hit with the...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 16:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-05-30-TheMentalStruggleofWFH/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-05-30-TheMentalStruggleofWFH/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Necronomicon Revived!</title>
        <description>
          Where the hell have I been? - 
          Well it’s been almost 2 years since I last did a post, or even blown the dust of this old necronomicon… Why? Overall it can be summed up in one word: Life Life Summed Up As with anything in life, you build a set of hobbies and activities, and each...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 14:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-05-30-WhereTheHell/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-05-30-WhereTheHell/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Git Good</title>
        <description>
          Basic Knowledge Dump of Git and Github - 
          This is just some testing grounds on understanding, utilising and getting better at Git. This is something I have been trying to do for a while so why not use it as a testing ground, but also share some notes. I dont really like the idea of “those who can’t...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-12-18-GitGood/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-12-18-GitGood/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>./helloWorld.sh</title>
        <description>
          Yet Another InfoSec Blog Poster - 
          Hello World! My first ever post using the beautiful-jekyll theme and gitpages setup! Why U do dis? Yet another Cyber Security Blog… I know. But I am hoping that posting the random shit I do can also intice the reader a little longer and be a little more engaged. Basically,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-12-14-helloWorld/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-12-14-helloWorld/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
